Finding Aid for the Alumni Relations Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Alumni Relations
multiple
University Archives
RG.0935
1 linear_feet
- Deceased Alumni
  - Brockman, Sidney J. (Box 0479, Folder 1)
  - Brockman, Whitfield W. (Box 0479, Folder 2)
  - Buchanan, Charles Henry (Box 0479, Folder 3)
  - DeWitt, John H. (1 of 3 Files) (Box 0479, Folder 4)
  - DeWitt, John H. (2 of 3 Files) (Box 0479, Folder 5)
  - DeWitt, John H. (3 of 3 Files) (Box 0479, Folder 6)
  - Drake, Robert (Box 0479, Folder 7)
  - Ford, Alex C. (Box 0479, Folder 8)
  - McTyeire, Holland N., Photo (Buiding where McTyeire preached not McTyeire himself) (Box 0479, Folder 9)
  - O'Kain, Paul Everett (Box 0479, Folder 10)
  - Rand, Frank, Photo (Box 0479, Folder 11)
  - Richardson, James D. (Box 0479, Folder 12)
  - Sanders, Joe Pilant, Photo (Box 0479, Folder 13)
  - Soo, Thomas P. H. (Box 0479, Folder 14)
  - Tsao, S. K. (Box 0479, Folder 15)
  - Whiteside, Fred W (Box 0479, Folder 16)
  - Whiteside, J. Lister (Box 0479, Folder 17)
  - Whiteside, John M. (Box 0479, Folder 18)
  - Whiteside, Joseph (Box 0479, Folder 19)
  - Whiteside, Warren T. (Box 0479, Folder 20)
  - Wills, William Ridley (Box 0479, Folder 21)
  - Beck, R. David (Box 0479, Folder 22)
  - Bodfish, Jeanne Stephenson (Box 0479, Folder 23)
  - Bottorff, Charles E. (Box 0479, Folder 24)
  - Bright, Hugh B. and Ann Elizbeth Rees (Box 0479, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Ruth Faw Pointer (Box 0479, Folder 26)
  - Buchanan, Fannie C. (Box 0479, Folder 27)
  - Brynn, Edward Cooke and Chris E. Hogan (Box 0479, Folder 28)
  - Carlisle, John Thomas and Allison C. Bruhl (Box 0479, Folder 29)
  - Chaffin, Ruth J., Photo (Box 0479, Folder 30)
  - Cook, Charles Eugene (Box 0479, Folder 31)
  - Corlette, Marvin Brown (Box 0479, Folder 32)
  - Davis, Warren W. (Box 0479, Folder 33)
  - Denham, Ralph M. and Virginia C. Harlan (Box 0479, Folder 34)
  - Dick, John H. (Box 0479, Folder 35)
  - Elston, Patricia Breland (Box 0479, Folder 36)
  - Fant, L. Glenn and Gladys S. (Box 0479, Folder 37)
  - Graves, Terry Calton (Box 0479, Folder 38)
  - Haddock, Samuel T. (Box 0479, Folder 39)
  - Hays, Spencer (Box 0479, Folder 40)
  - Helguera, J. Leon and Byrd S. (Box 0479, Folder 41)
  - Holbein, Richard E. (Box 0479, Folder 42)
  - Hustead, James Hope (Box 0479, Folder 43)
  - Jeffries, Lewis Mitchell (Box 0479, Folder 44)
  - Johnson, Vincent E. (Box 0479, Folder 45)
  - Johnson, Virgina Perry (Box 0479, Folder 46)
  - Johnson, W. Andrew (Box 0479, Folder 47)
  - Johnson, W. Clint (Box 0479, Folder 48)
  - Johnson, W. R. (Box 0479, Folder 49)
  - Johnson, Wade Cook (Box 0479, Folder 50)
  - Alumni Files: Johnson, Wallace - Williams, D. (Box 0480)
  - Abbott, Rush Pulliam, Special Collections copy: The gift of Mary Margaret an (Box 2621, Folder 1)
  - Abel, William J. (Box 2621, Folder 2)
  - Abel, William Lee (Box 2621, Folder 3)
  - Abercrombie, Eugene (Box 2621, Folder 4)
  - Abernathy, Alfred Harris (Box 2621, Folder 5)
  - Abernathy, Berry Chapman (Box 2621, Folder 6)
  - Abernathy, Ernest H. (Box 2621, Folder 7)
  - Abernathy, Gilbert Taylor (Box 2621, Folder 8)
  - Abernathy, James Robert (Box 2621, Folder 9)
  - Abernathy, Shields (Box 2621, Folder 10)
  - Abernathy, Wallace Warren (Box 2621, Folder 11)
  - Abney, Clarence Lee (Box 2621, Folder 12)
  - Abney, Olympia McKelvey (Box 2621, Folder 13)
  - Abraham, Joseph Lester (Box 2621, Folder 14)
  - Abrahams, Johanna Lichtenfels (Box 2621, Folder 15)
  - Acklen, Mrs. J. H. (Jeannette Tillotson) (Box 2621, Folder 16)
  - Acklen, Richard (Box 2621, Folder 17)
  - Ackley, John Bernard (Box 2621, Folder 18)
  - Acton, William Henson (Box 2621, Folder 19)
  - Acuff, Mr. and Mrs. Thomas Howard (Box 2621, Folder 20)
  - Adachi, Chapman Kinnosuke (Box 2621, Folder 21)
  - Adair, Eugene F. (Box 2621, Folder 22)
  - Adams, Adam Gillespie and Faith Yow (Wife) (Box 2621, Folder 23)
  - Adams, Adam Gillespie and Faith Yow (Wife) (Box 2621, Folder 24)
  - Adams, Adam Gillespie and Faith Yow (Wife) (Box 2621, Folder 25)
  - Adams, Alfred Armstrong (Box 2621, Folder 26)
  - Adams, Alfred Thompson (Box 2621, Folder 27)
  - Adams, Arthur Lambert (Box 2621, Folder 28)
  - Adams, Charles Cleveland (Box 2621, Folder 29)
  - Adams, Clarence Ernest (Box 2621, Folder 30)
  - Adams, David Porterfield (Box 2621, Folder 31)
  - Adams, Mrs. Edward Reeves (Frances Elizabeth Wynns) (Box 2621, Folder 32)
  - Adams, Edwin Brown (Box 2621, Folder 33)
  - Adams, Edwin Gaillard (Box 2621, Folder 34)
  - Adams, George Elliott and Katherine Abbott Ogden (Wife) (Box 2621, Folder 35)
  - Adams, Georgia Butler (Box 2621, Folder 36)
  - Adams, Howell Elliott (Box 2621, Folder 37)
  - Adams, Hugh Robert (Box 2621, Folder 38)
  - Adams, James Henry (Box 2621, Folder 39)
  - Adams, James Louis (Box 2621, Folder 40)
  - Adams, James Moore (Box 2621, Folder 41)
  - Adams, James Ryan (Box 2621, Folder 42)
  - Adams, Jesse Franklin (Box 2621, Folder 43)
  - Adams, Joe Samford (Box 2621, Folder 44)
  - Adams, John Ball (Box 2621, Folder 45)
  - Adams, Julien W. (Box 2621, Folder 46)
  - Adams, Justin Orpheus (Box 2621, Folder 47)
  - Adams, Marion Strickler (Box 2621, Folder 48)
  - Adams, Morton Boyte (Box 2621, Folder 49)
  - Adams, Ralph (Box 2621, Folder 50)
  - Adams, Richard Elder (Box 2621, Folder 51)
  - Adams, Ruby Vernon (Box 2621, Folder 52)
  - Adams, Mrs. William Leroy (Ruby Corinne Lanier) (Box 2621, Folder 53)
  - Adams, Stanley R. (Box 2621, Folder 54)
  - Adams, Thomas Conley (Box 2621, Folder 55)
  - Adams, Thomas Reynolds (Box 2621, Folder 56)
  - Adams, Will Thomas (Box 2621, Folder 57)
  - Adams, William Powell (Box 2621, Folder 58)
  - Adamson, William Bluford (Box 2621, Folder 59)
  - Aden, William Clinton (Box 2621, Folder 60)
  - Ader, Meredith William (Box 2621, Folder 61)
  - Adkerson, J. B. (Box 2621, Folder 62)
  - Adkins, James Howard (Box 2621, Folder 63)
  - Adkisson, Charles Noble (Box 2621, Folder 64)
  - Adkisson, James E. (Box 2621, Folder 65)
  - Adkisson, Jerry King (Box 2621, Folder 66)
  - Adkisson, Marcie N. (Box 2621, Folder 67)
  - Ahrens, Henry H. (Box 2621, Folder 68)
  - Aita, Aloysius Angelo (Box 2621, Folder 69)
  - Akazawa, Motozo (Box 2621, Folder 70)
  - Aker, Guila M. (Box 2621, Folder 71)
  - Aker, John Edwards (Box 2621, Folder 72)
  - Akers, James Clark (Box 2621, Folder 73)
  - Akin, Homer Alexander (Box 2621, Folder 74)
  - Akin, Jackson Grover (Box 2621, Folder 75)
  - Albers, Frazier Walker (Box 2621, Folder 76)
  - Albes, Charles Edward (Box 2621, Folder 77)
  - Albright, Jacob Karl (Box 2621, Folder 78)
  - Albright, Sara Celeste (Box 2621, Folder 79)
  - Alder, James Harley (Box 2621, Folder 80)
  - Alder, Max (Box 2621, Folder 81)
  - Alexander, Albert May (Box 2621, Folder 82)
  - Alexander, Clay Shelton (Box 2621, Folder 83)
  - Alexander, Gwynne Wilson (Box 2621, Folder 84)
  - Alexander, Harry Lee (Box 2621, Folder 85)
  - Alexander, Harvey C. (Box 2621, Folder 86)
  - Alexander, Harvey C. (Junior) (Box 2621, Folder 86)
  - Alexander, Horace Edward (Box 2621, Folder 87)
  - Alexander, James Frederick (Box 2621, Folder 88)
  - Alexander, James L. (Box 2621, Folder 89)
  - Alexander, Robert Lee and Roberta Smith (Wife) (Box 2621, Folder 90)
  - Alexander, Ross Coleman and Dorothy Lanier Hailey (Wife) (Box 2621, Folder 91)
  - Alexander, Ryce Pierce (Box 2621, Folder 92)
  - Alexander, Sadie Shofner (Mrs. Clarence F. Alexander) (Box 2621, Folder 93)
  - Alexander, Samuel Walker (Box 2621, Folder 94)
  - Alexander, Truman Hudson (Box 2621, Folder 95)
  - Alexander, Vance J. (Folder 1 of 6) (Box 2621, Folder 96)
  - Alexander, Vance J. (Folder 2 of 6) (Box 2621, Folder 97)
  - Alexander, Vance J. (Folder 3 of 6) (Box 2621, Folder 98)
  - Alexander, Vance J. (Folder 4 of 6) (Box 2621, Folder 99)
  - Alexander, Vance J. (Folder 5 of 6) (Box 2622, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, Vance J. (Folder 6 of 6) (Box 2622, Folder 2)
  - Alexander, Will Winton (Box 2622, Folder 3)
  - Alexander, William Mitchell (Box 2622, Folder 4)
  - Alexander, William Wallace (Box 2622, Folder 5)
  - Alexandria, John F. (Box 2622, Folder 6)
  - Aley, Polly Parrish (Mrs. Jerome Arnold Aley) (Box 2622, Folder 7)
  - Alford, Fountain Ellis (Box 2622, Folder 8)
  - Alford, Joseph William (Box 2622, Folder 9)
  - Alger, Richard Barrett (Box 2622, Folder 10)
  - Algood, Alfred (Box 2622, Folder 11)
  - Allan, James Stockdell (Box 2622, Folder 12)
  - Allan, William Presley (Box 2622, Folder 13)
  - Alldredge, H. H. (Box 2622, Folder 14)
  - Allen, Alfred Alexander (Box 2622, Folder 15)
  - Allen, Anderson Braxton (Box 2622, Folder 16)
  - Allen, Asa Ward (Box 2622, Folder 17)
  - Allen, Benjamin Lee (Box 2622, Folder 18)
  - Allen, Beverly Whipple (Box 2622, Folder 19)
  - Allen, Charles H. (Box 2622, Folder 20)
  - Allen, Charles Tyler (Box 2622, Folder 21)
  - Allen, Edmund Black (Box 2622, Folder 22)
  - Allen, Mrs. Edward H. (Adele T. Irwin) (Box 2622, Folder 23)
  - Allen, Frank C. (Box 2622, Folder 24)
  - Allen, Grandison Greer (Box 2622, Folder 25)
  - Allen, H. M. (Box 2622, Folder 26)
  - Allen, Harry Stanley (Box 2622, Folder 27)
  - Allen, Horace Leonard and Mary Eleanor Hall (Wife) (Box 2622, Folder 28)
  - Allen, James Alexander (Box 2622, Folder 29)
  - Allen, John D. (Box 2622, Folder 30)
  - Allen, John Howard (Box 2622, Folder 31)
  - Allen, John Seay (Box 2622, Folder 32)
  - Allen, Miller O. (Box 2622, Folder 33)
  - Allen, Percy A. (Box 2622, Folder 34)
  - Allen, R. M. (Box 2622, Folder 35)
  - Allen, Mrs. R. O. (Box 2622, Folder 36)
  - Allen, Robert E. (Box 2622, Folder 37)
  - Allen, Robert Lee (Box 2622, Folder 38)
  - Allen, Wharton Harwell (Box 2622, Folder 39)
  - Allen, Wilbur Price (Box 2622, Folder 40)
  - Alley, Ernest Hayes (Herc) (Box 2622, Folder 41)
  - Alley, Roy Farmer (Box 2622, Folder 42)
  - Alley, William H. (Box 2622, Folder 43)
  - Allgood, Jackson Lee (Box 2622, Folder 44)
  - Allison, Grady M. (Box 2622, Folder 45)
  - Allison, Granville (Box 2622, Folder 46)
  - Allison, Grayson (Box 2622, Folder 47)
  - Allred, C. S. (Box 2622, Folder 48)
  - Alshuler, Jerome L. (Box 2622, Folder 49)
  - Alsobrook, John Walter (Box 2622, Folder 50)
  - Alsobrook, William Lewis (Box 2622, Folder 51)
  - Alsup, Orville Mortimer (Box 2622, Folder 52)
  - Althanser, Nathaniel L. (Box 2622, Folder 53)
  - Altman, John Thomas (Box 2622, Folder 54)
  - Altman, John Thompson (Box 2622, Folder 55)
  - Altsheler, Joseph A. (Box 2622, Folder 56)
  - Alverson, Lonnie Gordon (Box 2622, Folder 57)
  - Amberg, William Boardman (Box 2622, Folder 58)
  - Ambrose, Henry Frizzell (Box 2622, Folder 59)
  - Ambrose, John Loften (Box 2622, Folder 60)
  - Ames, Allen M. (Box 2622, Folder 61)
  - Ames, Charles Bismark (Box 2622, Folder 62)
  - Ames, James L. (Box 2622, Folder 63)
  - Ames, William Goodson (Box 2622, Folder 64)
  - Amis, Agnes (Box 2622, Folder 65)
  - Amis, Charles Boothe (Box 2622, Folder 66)
  - Amis, John (Jack) E. (Box 2622, Folder 67)
  - Amis, Lewis Randolph (Junior) (Box 2622, Folder 68)
  - Amis, Lewis Randolph (Box 2622, Folder 69)
  - Amis, Reese Thomas (Box 2622, Folder 70)
  - Ammerman, Jonathan Edward (Box 2622, Folder 71)
  - Anders, Percy C. (Box 2622, Folder 72)
  - Anderson, Augustus Edwin and Katherine (Wife) (Box 2622, Folder 73)
  - Anderson, Charles (Box 2622, Folder 74)
  - Anderson, Charles Franklin (Box 2622, Folder 75)
  - Anderson, Cornelius A. (Box 2622, Folder 76)
  - Anderson, Douglas (Box 2622, Folder 77)
  - Anderson, Edwin Brown (Box 2622, Folder 78)
  - Anderson, Ernest Oliver (Box 2622, Folder 79)
  - Anderson, Erwin Patton (Box 2622, Folder 80)
  - Anderson, Eugene (and Mrs. Anderson) (Box 2622, Folder 81)
  - Anderson, Glenn P. (Box 2622, Folder 82)
  - Anderson, Gloria Rees (Box 2622, Folder 83)
  - Anderson, Harry Warren (Box 2622, Folder 84)
  - Anderson, Henry Melville (Box 2622, Folder 85)
  - Anderson, Herman Howard (Box 2622, Folder 86)
  - Anderson, James A. (Box 2622, Folder 87)
  - Anderson, James H. (Box 2622, Folder 88)
  - Anderson, James Isaac (Box 2622, Folder 89)
  - Anderson, James McMullen (Box 2622, Folder 90)
  - Anderson, James Sumpter (Box 2622, Folder 91)
  - Anderson, James Thomas (Box 2622, Folder 92)
  - Anderson, Jesse Andrew (Box 2622, Folder 93)
  - Anderson, John Cecil (Box 2622, Folder 94)
  - Anderson, John Davis (Box 2622, Folder 95)
  - Anderson, John McFerrin (Box 2622, Folder 96)
  - Anderson, John T. (Box 2622, Folder 97)
  - Anderson, Joseph Drake (Box 2622, Folder 98)
  - Anderson, Joseph Earl (Box 2622, Folder 99)
  - Anderson, Joseph John (Box 2622, Folder 100)
  - Anderson, Katherine (Box 2622, Folder 101)
  - Anderson, Kurtz King (Box 2622, Folder 102)
  - Anderson, Laurence Desiax (Box 2622, Folder 103)
  - Anderson, Lewis Ridley (Box 2622, Folder 104)
  - Anderson, Milton Dewitt (Box 2622, Folder 105)
  - Anderson, Milton J. (Box 2622, Folder 106)
  - Anderson, Mrs. Oren Kerr (Box 2622, Folder 107)
  - Anderson, Paul Gordon (Box 2622, Folder 108)
  - Anderson, Preston Thomas (Box 2622, Folder 109)
  - Anderson, Ray Avalon (Box 2622, Folder 110)
  - Anderson, Robert Lee (Box 2622, Folder 111)
  - Anderson, Robert Morrison (Box 2622, Folder 112)
  - Anderson, Robert Poindexter (Box 2622, Folder 113)
  - Anderson, Samuel Newton (Box 2622, Folder 114)
  - Anderson, Thomas Ervin (Box 2622, Folder 115)
  - Anderson, Walton Humphrey (Box 2622, Folder 116)
  - Anderson, William Bush (Box 2622, Folder 117)
  - Anderson, William Carroll (Box 2622, Folder 118)
  - Anderson, William Edward (Box 2622, Folder 119)
  - Anderson, William Joseph (Junior) (Box 2622, Folder 120)
  - Anderson, William Joseph (Box 2622, Folder 121)
  - Anderson, William Madison (Box 2622, Folder 122)
  - Anderson, William Thomas (Box 2622, Folder 123)
  - Anderson, Woodford Dulaney (Box 2622, Folder 124)
  - Anderton, Murrell William (Junior) (Box 2622, Folder 125)
  - Anderton, Murrell William (Box 2622, Folder 126)
  - Anderton, Thomas B. (Box 2622, Folder 127)
  - Andrews, Edward C. (Box 2622, Folder 128)
  - Andrews, Forrest (Folder 1 of 3) (Box 2622, Folder 129)
  - Andrews, Forrest (Folder 2 of 3) (Box 2622, Folder 130)
  - Andrews, Forrest (Folder 3 of 3) (Box 2622, Folder 131)
  - Andrews, Fred C. (Box 2622, Folder 132)
  - Andrews, Garnett Stith (Box 2622, Folder 133)
  - Andrews, Glenn (Box 2622, Folder 134)
  - Andrews, Greg (Box 2622, Folder 135)
  - Andrews, Henry James (Box 2622, Folder 136)
  - Andrews, James David (Box 2622, Folder 137)
  - Andrews, James L. (Box 2622, Folder 138)
  - Andrews, John A. (Box 2622, Folder 139)
  - Andrews, Kenneth R. and Katherine Graves (Wife) (Box 2622, Folder 140)
  - Andrews, Ralph James (Box 2622, Folder 141)
  - Andrews, Thomas Gayleon (Box 2622, Folder 142)
  - Andrews, William Valery (Box 2622, Folder 143)
  - Anglin, Byron Chesterfield and Carolyn Drew (Wife) (Box 2622, Folder 144)
  - Ansley, Dick (Box 2622, Folder 145)
  - Ansley, Mildred Bond (Box 2623, Folder 1)
  - Anthony, Charles Ross (Box 2623, Folder 2)
  - Anthony, Daniel Herbert and Helen Lawrence (Wife) (Box 2623, Folder 3)
  - Anthony, Dorothy Barber Vickers (Mrs. James T. Anthony) (Box 2623, Folder 4)
  - Anthony, Harlan Ward (Box 2623, Folder 5)
  - Anthony, Thomas Melville (Box 2623, Folder 6)
  - Anthony, Walter (Box 2623, Folder 7)
  - Apperson, John Wesley (Box 2623, Folder 8)
  - Applegate, Elmore T. (Box 2623, Folder 9)
  - Appleton, Hugh Lowns (Box 2623, Folder 10)
  - Applewhite, Abner Meek (Box 2623, Folder 11)
  - Applewhite, Calvin Crawford (Box 2623, Folder 12)
  - Applewhite, Joe Davis (Box 2623, Folder 13)
  - Applewhite, John C. (Box 2623, Folder 14)
  - Arant, Roscoe (Box 2623, Folder 15)
  - Arbery, W. B. (Box 2623, Folder 16)
  - Archer, David B. (Box 2623, Folder 17)
  - Archer, George Ferguson (Box 2623, Folder 18)
  - Archer, John George (Box 2623, Folder 19)
  - Archer, Verley Mae (Box 2623, Folder 20)
  - Archie, Andrew Nathan (Box 2623, Folder 21)
  - Argo, Eugene (Box 2623, Folder 22)
  - Argo, John R. (Box 2623, Folder 23)
  - Armbrister, Victor Stradley (Box 2623, Folder 24)
  - Armistead, George Harrison (Box 2623, Folder 25)
  - Armistead, George Harrison (Junior) (Box 2623, Folder 26)
  - Armistead, James Cate and Oprah Henkel (Wife) (Box 2623, Folder 27)
  - Armistead, Leonard Hearn (Junior) and Alyne Queener (Wife) (Box 2623, Folder 28)
  - Armistead, Leonard Hearn (Box 2623, Folder 29)
  - Armistead, Robert A. (Box 2623, Folder 30)
  - Armistead, William S. H. (Box 2623, Folder 31)
  - Armistead, Wirt Mayo (Box 2623, Folder 32)
  - Armstrong, Clude B. (Box 2623, Folder 33)
  - Armstrong, Edward Livingston (Box 2623, Folder 34)
  - Armstrong, James Loudon (Box 2623, Folder 35)
  - Armstrong, Joseph C. (Box 2623, Folder 36)
  - Armstrong, Florence Hayes (Mrs. Robert W. Armstrong) (Box 2623, Folder 37)
  - Arnett, Samuel Thomas (Box 2623, Folder 38)
  - Arning, Robert Alfred and Martha Buford Woodcock (Wife) (Box 2623, Folder 39)
  - Arnold, Benjamin Clayton (Box 2623, Folder 40)
  - Arnold, Carl Edison (Box 2623, Folder 41)
  - Arnold, Earl C. (Box 2623, Folder 42)
  - Arnold, John Martin (Box 2623, Folder 43)
  - Arnold, Julia P. (Box 2623, Folder 44)
  - Arnold, Kenneth L. (Box 2623, Folder 45)
  - Arnold, Lloyd L. (Box 2623, Folder 46)
  - Arnold, Moody Warren (Box 2623, Folder 47)
  - Arnold, Polie E. (Box 2623, Folder 48)
  - Arnold, Ralph D. (Box 2623, Folder 49)
  - Arrants, Mary (Box 2623, Folder 50)
  - Arrants, Nathan Absolom (Box 2623, Folder 51)
  - Arrants, William Ross (Box 2623, Folder 52)
  - Arterbury, Roy L. and Hazel Platt (Wife) (Box 2623, Folder 53)
  - Arthur, Francis (Frank) C. (Box 2623, Folder 54)
  - Arthur, Russell W. (Box 2623, Folder 55)
  - Ashburn, John Martin (Box 2623, Folder 56)
  - Ashby, Josiah Jefferson and Mary Walker Quarles (Wife) (Box 2623, Folder 57)
  - Ashford, Emma Louise Hindle (Box 2623, Folder 58)
  - Ashford, Henry Stephen (Box 2623, Folder 59)
  - Ashford, John (Box 2623, Folder 60)
  - Ashley, Robert Grady (Box 2623, Folder 61)
  - Ashley, Thomas Everett (Box 2623, Folder 62)
  - Ashley, William Garrett (Box 2623, Folder 63)
  - Askew, Burgess Bethel (Box 2623, Folder 64)
  - Askew, John Clarence (Box 2623, Folder 65)
  - Askew, Laurin Bryan (Box 2623, Folder 66)
  - Askew, Pierce Ford (Box 2623, Folder 67)
  - Askew, Wesley Lafayette (Box 2623, Folder 68)
  - Atchison, Kenneth C. (Box 2623, Folder 69)
  - Athearn, Carl Rhea (Box 2623, Folder 70)
  - Atkeisson, John Edward Hall (Box 2623, Folder 71)
  - Atkin, Clay Brown (Box 2623, Folder 72)
  - Atkins, Daniel F. Ewell (Box 2623, Folder 73)
  - Atkins, James E. (Box 2623, Folder 74)
  - Atkins, James R. (Box 2623, Folder 75)
  - Atkins, John D. Clinton (Box 2623, Folder 76)
  - Atkins, Orman Hensley (Box 2623, Folder 77)
  - Atkinson, Benjamin Franklin (Box 2623, Folder 78)
  - Atkinson, Charles D. (Box 2623, Folder 79)
  - Atkinson, Fitzgerald (Box 2623, Folder 80)
  - Atkinson, George Sublett (Box 2623, Folder 81)
  - Atkinson, Katherine Swain (Box 2623, Folder 82)
  - Atkinson, Richard Merrill (Box 2623, Folder 83)
  - Atkinson, Warren (Box 2623, Folder 84)
  - Atlee, Emil G. (Box 2623, Folder 85)
  - Atlee, James H. (Box 2623, Folder 86)
  - Attkisson, Eugene R. (Box 2623, Folder 87)
  - Aubel, Dorothy Adele Longhurst (Mrs. Lee Francis Aubel) (Box 2623, Folder 88)
  - Audrain, Helen J. (Box 2623, Folder 89)
  - Augustine, Lewis Samuel (Box 2623, Folder 90)
  - Augustus, Nicholas G. (Box 2623, Folder 91)
  - Ault, Otto Thurman (Box 2623, Folder 92)
  - Austell, Curtis Williams (Box 2623, Folder 93)
  - Austin, Emmet E. (Box 2623, Folder 94)
  - Austin, Garnett (Box 2623, Folder 95)
  - Austin, George Lafayette (Box 2623, Folder 96)
  - Austin, Harry Williams (Box 2623, Folder 97)
  - Austin, Hayden G. (Box 2623, Folder 98)
  - Austin, Homer Harris and Margaret Louise Yound (Wife) (Box 2623, Folder 99)
  - Austin, James Clifford (Box 2623, Folder 100)
  - Austin, John Luther (Box 2623, Folder 101)
  - Austin, Mickie Perry (Box 2623, Folder 102)
  - Austin, Sarah Staley (Mrs. Rankin A. Austin) (Box 2623, Folder 103)
  - Austin, Theodore Roe (Box 2623, Folder 104)
  - Austin, Tolliver Louis (Box 2623, Folder 105)
  - Austin, Will Ross (Box 2623, Folder 106)
  - Austin, William Garnett (Box 2623, Folder 107)
  - Auten, Donald Roland (Box 2623, Folder 108)
  - Auten, Lawrence (Box 2623, Folder 109)
  - Avent, Frank (Box 2623, Folder 110)
  - Avery, Allen Steinwehr (Box 2623, Folder 111)
  - Avery, John Buchanan (Box 2623, Folder 112)
  - Avery, Mary Brandon Johnson (Mrs. Omer H. Avery) (Box 2623, Folder 113)
  - Awtrey, Hugh Hanna (Box 2623, Folder 114)
  - Axtell, Phillip Phillips (Box 2623, Folder 115)
  - Aycock, Thomas Jesse (Box 2623, Folder 116)
  - Ayers, William Norton (Box 2623, Folder 117)
  - Aylen, Walter Carter (Box 2623, Folder 118)
  - Ayres, E. Hanes (Junior) (Box 2623, Folder 119)
  - Ayres, E. Hanes (Box 2623, Folder 120)
  - Babcock, Drury Abel (Box 2623, Folder 121)
  - Babcock, Sidney H. (Junior) and Margaret Miriam (Wife) (Box 2623, Folder 122)
  - Babcock, Sidney H., III (Box 2623, Folder 123)
  - Bachman, George E. (Box 2623, Folder 124)
  - Bachman, Joseph S. (Box 2623, Folder 125)
  - Back, James Bernard (Box 2623, Folder 126)
  - Bacon, Carrington C. (Box 2623, Folder 127)
  - Bacon, George William (Box 2623, Folder 128)
  - Bacon, Roy Brown (Box 2623, Folder 129)
  - Bacon, William James (Box 2623, Folder 130)
  - Bacon, Mrs. William (Elizabeth Upthegrove) (Box 2623, Folder 131)
  - Baer, Irwin H. (Box 2623, Folder 132)
  - Baer, Mary Elizabeth (Box 2623, Folder 133)
  - Bagby, John H. C. (Box 2623, Folder 134)
  - Bagwell, Mary Elizabeth Monroe (Mrs. John C. Bagwell) (Box 2623, Folder 135)
  - Bailes, Edward Thomas (Box 2623, Folder 136)
  - Bailey, Archie Elroy (Box 2623, Folder 137)
  - Bailey, C. V. (Box 2623, Folder 138)
  - Bailey, Clyde L. (Box 2623, Folder 139)
  - Bailey, Conrad Oswald (Box 2623, Folder 140)
  - Bailey, Dyce (Box 2623, Folder 141)
  - Bailey, Ferriss Clay (Box 2623, Folder 142)
  - Bailey, George Hill (Box 2623, Folder 143)
  - Bailey, Harry Lee and Betty Scrivner (Wife) (Box 2623, Folder 144)
  - Bailey, Henry Mayberry (Box 2623, Folder 145)
  - Bailey, J. Carlyle (Box 2623, Folder 146)
  - Bailey, J. Mansfield (Box 2623, Folder 147)
  - Bailey, J. Russell (Box 2623, Folder 148)
  - Bailey, Jesse Hugh (Box 2623, Folder 149)
  - Bailey, Jesse Lee (Box 2623, Folder 150)
  - Bailey, John Philip (Box 2623, Folder 151)
  - Bailey, Kenneth Karnes (Box 2623, Folder 152)
  - Bailey, Lucien Lucius (Box 2623, Folder 153)
  - Bailey, Preston Perkins (Box 2623, Folder 154)
  - Bailey, Robert Albert (Box 2624, Folder 1)
  - Bailey, Robert Kline (Box 2624, Folder 2)
  - Bailey, Thomas Jennings (Box 2624, Folder 3)
  - Bailey, William (Box 2624, Folder 4)
  - Bailey, William M. (Box 2624, Folder 5)
  - Bains, William T. (Box 2624, Folder 6)
  - Baird, George Dewey (Box 2624, Folder 7)
  - Baird, Geren McLemore (Box 2624, Folder 8)
  - Baird, Glen M. (Box 2624, Folder 9)
  - Baird, Jospeh Jay (Box 2624, Folder 10)
  - Baird, Lewis Foster (Box 2624, Folder 11)
  - Baird, Perry Cossart (Box 2624, Folder 12)
  - Baird, William Edward (Box 2624, Folder 13)
  - Bakay, Arpad (Box 2624, Folder 14)
  - Baker, Allan Moore (Box 2624, Folder 15)
  - Baker, Clark Everett (Box 2624, Folder 16)
  - Baker, Clem N. (Box 2624, Folder 17)
  - Baker, Daniel Harris (Box 2624, Folder 18)
  - Baker, David Hume (Box 2624, Folder 19)
  - Baker, Elwood (Box 2624, Folder 20)
  - Baker, Everett Harold and Mildred Smith (Wife) (Box 2624, Folder 21)
  - Baker, George Cleveland (Box 2624, Folder 22)
  - Baker, Isaac Boulds (Box 2624, Folder 23)
  - Baker, James Frank (Box 2624, Folder 24)
  - Baker, John Dhot (Box 2624, Folder 25)
  - Baker, John Elliott (Box 2624, Folder 26)
  - Baker, Julia Rodgers (Box 2624, Folder 27)